mensnewsdaily.com 2008-05-11

# Privacy Policy | MND: News and Commentary Since 2001

**MNDwire**

December 9, 2007 at 1:26 pm · Filed under [Vox Populi](http://mensnewsdaily.com/category/vox-populi/ "View all posts in Vox Populi")

## Privacy Policy

MensNewsDaily (MND) takes your privacy seriously. Please note changes to our privacy policy.  
_  
NOTICE: [Click here](http://onguardonline.gov/) for practical tips from the federal government and the technology industry to help you guard against Internet fraud, secure your computer and protect your personal information._

MND collects personal information when you register with our site. MND may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.

MND does not rent or sell personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with MND . These companies may use your personal information to help communicate with you about matters we think may interest you.
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Yahoo!’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
  * We transfer information about you if MND is acquired by or merged with another company.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

MND may update this policy. Please note [this page](http://mensnewsdaily.com/privacy-policy/) for any changes to our privacy policy.

**Who can I ask if I have any additional questions?**  
If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, contact editor(at)MensNewsDaily.com.

[Permalink](http://mensnewsdaily.com/privacy-policy/ "Permanent link to Privacy Policy") | **[](http://mensnewsdaily.com/privacy-policy/printpage/ "Print This Page") [Print This Page](http://mensnewsdaily.com/privacy-policy/printpage/ "Print This Page") ** | **Other posts by[MNDwire](http://mensnewsdaily.com/author/MNDwire/ "Posts by MNDwire")**

Comments are closed.
